wrzc.org 2012-02-14

# Privacy Policy Statement

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

At wrzc.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by wrzc.org and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, wrzc.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites. wrzc.org has no control over the content exhibited on these sites, or the administration of them. Use of such sites is subject to each site's unique privacy policy.

### Google Analytics

Visitors to wrzc.org who have javascript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects the following types of information from users:

Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number, Type of operating system, Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen), Javascript support, Flash version, Screen resolution, Network location and IP address, Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data., Hostname, Bandwidth (internet connection speed), Time of visit, Pages visited, Time spent on each page of the website, Referring site statistics, The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website), Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) , This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors, however we will use this data for marketing purposes. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to the website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website.

This data DOES NOT include any personalized identification information such as:

Names, Phone Numbers, Email Addresses, Mailing Addresses, Social Security Numbers, Bank Account Numbers, Credit Card Information

### Changes to this privacy policy

wrzc.org has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us

This document was last updated on November 5, 2011
